She owes this land a body.
Lovely, Dark, and Deep is a horror film directed by Teresa Sutherland.
Lennon, a new back-country ranger, travels alone through the dangerous wilderness, hoping to
uncover the origins of a tragedy that has haunted her since she was a child.
Lennon, played by Georgina Campbell.
Jackson, played by Nick Blood.
Zhang, played by Wai Ching Ho.
James Moore, played by Edgar Morais.
Mother, played by Ana Sofia Martins.
Varney, played by Søren Hellerup.
Lovely, Dark, and Deep is a 2023 American horror film written and
directed by Teresa Sutherland in her feature directorial debut.
Starring Georgina Campbell, Nick Blood, and Wai Ching Ho, the film follows Lennon (Campbell), a backcountry ranger who, hoping to uncover the origins of a
tragedy that has haunted her since childhood, begins her new job at Arvores National Park, where several employees and hikers have gone missing.
Lovely, Dark, and Deep premiered at the Fantasia International Film Festival on July 23, 2023, and was theatrically released in the United
States on February 22, 2024, to critical acclaim, with particular praise for Campbell's performance and Sutherland's direction.
The film explores themes of national park, camp,
park ranger, missing person, absurd.
The tone is dark.